http://www.kicker.com/privacy-policy

We use cookies to personalize content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyze our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners who may combine it with other information that you've provided to them or that they've collected from your use of their services. You consent to our cookies if you continue to use this website. Check out our Privacy Policy.
Got It!
Toggle navigation
KICKER
Products
Car Audio
Subwoofers
Amplifiers
Key Technology
Speakers
Stillwater Designs Privacy Policy
Protecting your privacy is important to us at Stillwater Designs. We hope the following will help you understand how we collect, use, and protect the personal information you provide on our Web site.
Information Collection
At times we may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal information, such as your email address and postal address, for purposes such as registering a new product, corresponding with us, registering at a site, making a purchase, entering a sweepstakes, or participating in an online survey. At no time will we share this information with anyone.
Information Use
When you supply KICKER with your personal information, we may use it to register your product or to send you information/materials you request from us. We may use the information to tell you about new products, services, and offers that you may find interesting. We may also use information that you have given us to learn more who uses KICKER products so we can develop products and services better suited to our customers' needs.
Data Security
KICKER is fully committed to data security. We have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information you provide to us online. However, while we make every effort to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit to us. In this regard, we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data while you are on the Internet.
Access to Other Web Sites
Stillwater Designs makes no representations whatsoever about any other Web site which you may access through this one. When you access a non-Stillwater Designs Web site, even one that may contain logos owned by Stillwater designs, please understand that it is independent from Stillwater Designs, and that Stillwater Designs has no control over the content, the privacy, or the security measures on that Web site. In addition, a link to a non-Stillwater Designs Web site does not mean that Stillwater Designs endorses or accepts any responsibility for the content, or the use, of such Web site. It is up to you to take precautions to ensure that whatever you select for your use is free of such items as viruses, worms, Trojan horses and other items of a destructive nature. IN NO EVENT WILL STILLWATER DESIGNS BE LIABLE TO ANY PARTY FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL OR OTHER CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES FOR ANY USE OF THIS WEB SITE, OR ON ANY OTHER HYPER LINKED WEB SITE, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY LOST PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF PROGRAMS OR OTHER DATA ON YOUR INFORMATION HANDLING SYSTEM OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF WE ARE EXPRESSLY ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
This privacy policy is subject to change at any time and without notice. For updates, please check here.
Privacy Policy | Return and Refund
© , Stillwater Designs. All rights reserved. Copyright and Trademark Notice.
